And here we have the
hazelnut, which is a cousin
of the macadamia nut.
Oh, and this is the
Kayla nut, named after
princess Kayla Dupree, who
became famous for throwing nuts
at poor people.
Okay, that's all the
time we have for, Gibby.
But I'm not done yet.
Yeah, you are. Take care.
Now, you may be asking
yourself, "do Carly and Sam
care about science?"
No.
But we do think it might
be fun to watch food rot.
Which is why we'd like to introduce
a new iCarly segment called...
Let's watch food rot.
[Applause]
Now, come check out what
we did to a peanut butter
and jelly sandwich.
Okay. Now, Sam and I
dismantled this peanut butter
and jelly sandwich that Sam
took from some kid at school.
Yeah, I'm the kid.
Gibby.
Now, our awesome technical
producer-- Fredaloopay.
--Has installed a special camera
that will constantly record
this sandwich over
the next four weeks.
Mm, 24/7.
And when the four weeks are up...
...Freddie's gonna speed up
the video... ...
So we can show you
the rotting of the sandwich...
...In only 30 seconds.
So if you're a loser... ...
At least you got that
to look forward to.
Okay.
That's all for this iCarly.
Till next time.
Bye.
And we're clear.
Oh.
Yes.
Yeah.
Good show, guys.
What up with that
Fredaloopay business?
Hey, Gibby. Are you ready?
Oh, hey. Uh, just a sec.
Let me grab my briefcase.
That's tasha?
Uh-huh.
And you're dating her?
Yeah, pretty much.
Let's hit it.
I told you she was hot.
Yeah, but you didn't
say she was that hot.
How does he get one of those?
I want one of those.
In 5, 4, 3, 2...
[music]
♪ I know you see ♪
♪ somehow the world ♪
♪ will change for me ♪
♪ and be so wonderful ♪
♪ live life, breathe air ♪
♪ I know somehow ♪
♪ we're gonna get there ♪
♪ and feel so wonderful ♪
♪ it's all for real ♪
♪ I'm telling you ♪
♪ just how I feel ♪
♪ so wake up ♪
♪ the members of my nation ♪
♪ it's your time to be ♪
♪ there's no change ♪
♪ unless you take one ♪
♪ it's the time to see ♪
♪ the brighter side ♪
♪ of every situation ♪
♪ some things are meant to be ♪
♪ so give your best ♪
♪ and leave the rest to me ♪
Hi.
What's going on?
I'm shredding newspapers
with an industrial
gasoline-powered paper shredder.
How was school?
I don't remember or care.
Man, why do they even make
these things anymore?
Some people still read newspapers.
Yeah, hobos and the elderly.
So why are you industrially
shredding newspapers?
'Cause that snooty art
critic oliver Dixon
from the Seattle tribune wrote a
mean review of my sculptures.
He did?
That jerk.
Yeah.
So I grabbed as many of these as
I could find and now I'm making
oliver Dixon's review feel this.
That felt nice.
Man, look at all the--
holy chiz on a chizel.
What?
"Spencer Shay of Seattle "died of
natural causes last Saturday."
It doesn't say that.
It says that.
Nice.
First, they insult my art
and then they call me dead,
which, incidentally, I'm not.
So are you gonna call the
tribune and yell at 'em?
Nah, who cares?
People don't read newspapers anymore.
Hey.
Uh, my mom can't find our newspaper.
You guys seen it?
All right, have fun at school.
I'll miss you.
You don't have to miss me.
Huh?
Check your phone.
New video message.
Click it.
What's up, tasha?
Who's thinkin' about you?
That's right.
This guy.
Oh, that is so sweet.
Yeah.
Hey, home fries.
Hi.
So, you guys comin'
to Carly's hobo party?
That sounds so fun.
How great is her attitude?
Come on, I'll walk you to your car.
How?
I...
I don't know.
[Music]
Hey.
Howdy.
You play the ukulele?
Yeah, a little.
Wow.
That's never been established.
So Spencer still mad about the
newspaper saying he was dead?
Nah, he was way more bummed
about the bad review
of his sculptures.
So where is Spence?
He went to the Seattle civic
center to help out that charity,
the angels of Seattle.
They're teaching sculpting
to underprivileged kids.
Nice.
You know, my mom was
an angel for a while
till they kicked her out.
Why?
They hated her.
Ah.
Hey, I gotta go up to the
studio and update some firmware
on our server.
Have fun, Captain techno.
[Knocking]
Coming.
Carly.
Oh, hey, mister...
Klemish, one apartment down.
Right. 7-c.
Yes. I came by to-- hey,
the door's locked.
The key is on top of the thingy.
My friend Freddie is trying
to-- I can't find it.
Come in.
I'll be right back.
What's the matter with you?
[Phone ringing]
Hi.
No, I'm making a condolence call.
Oh, a young artist named Spencer
Shay who died last Saturday.
His poor little sister.
Yeah, just order me a turkey
sandwich with mustard and pickles.
Hey. Sorry.
My friend Freddie was bein' spazzy.
So what's up?
I was so sorry to read about
Spencer in the paper.
Oh, yeah.
It was really negative, wasn't it?
Yes, well, uh, but-- I
mean, I guess it happens
to every artist sooner
or later, right?
I suppose.
But this was so soon,
too--so unexpected.
Yeah, Spencer sure didn't expect it.
But he's all right now.
He's sculpting with the angels.
That's a great way to look at it.
Uh, I don't know if Spencer told you,
but I talked to him about buying
his pencil sculpture before he--
you know?
Oh. You mean this one?
Yes.
Well, did you and Spencer
agree on a price?
Not really.
He mentioned 500, but we
were still discussing it.
Oh. Well, shoot, I
wish he was here.
Oh, we all wish Spencer was here.
[Buzzer]
One sec.
What, Lewbert?
Delivery comin' up in the elevator.
Okay.
[Makes sounds]
Anyway, if Spencer said 500, I'm sure...
You know what?
I'm just gonna give you 2,000 for it.
2,000?
Yes.
When artists are gone, their artwork
becomes much more valuable.
Right. Right. What?
I'm so sorry.
What do you mean by... hi.
Flowers for Carly Shay?
That's me.
I'm sorry for your loss.
What'd I lose?
Hay-dee ho-dee doober.
Hi.
Who are the flowers from?
I don't know.
I didn't read the card yet.
Here.
"Carly, I'm so sorry "for your loss.
"Spencer will be dearly missed.
Principal Franklin."
That's weird.
It sounds like he thinks
that-- you're dead.
Say what?
The obituary in the paper,
people think you're dead.
Ah, that's it.
I'm gonna call that newspaper.
Now I know why Mr. Klemish gave me $2,000
for your pencil sculpture.
What? 2,000 what?
Two g's.
But I told klemish I'd probably
sell it for around 500.
Well, he said artists get
more money for their work
after they're dead.
[Phone ringing]
Hello?
No, I'm sorry, Spencer is dead.
[Music]
Thanks, thanks for
coming to my hobo party.
Thanks. Bye. See you, guys.
I heard the door slam.
Party over?
Yes, you can come out now.
Yay, I'm starved.
Oh.
Why didn't you just come
out during the party?
'Cause I'm dead.
Don't poke me.
He's not dead.
He's just pretending to
be so he can trick people
into spending more money for his art.
It was not my idea.
I'm a victim of poor newspapermanship.
[Makes sounds]
Hey, you want us to help you clean up?
Thanks, sure.
I'll check and see if
the couch is okay.
Aahh, this might take awhile.
Hey, will you help me with something?
Sure.
You know, Gibby's
birthday is next week.
Yeah, he handed out these flyers.
Well, I wanna get him a video camera.
Can you give me some advice?
Yeah, I got a little one up in
the studio that'd be perfect.
Come on up, I'll show you.
Okay.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, so this
is Gibby's girlfriend?
Yeah.
Uh-huh.
Interesting.
Why?
See?
Palm size, with an optical
zoom, flash memory,
it's got 720p high-def.
It can also take-- Gibby likes
to make videos of his cat.
Is it good for that?
Yes, it works on cats.
Oh, awesome.
[Phone rings]
Oh, Gibby's looking for me.
I should get back downstairs.
Um, why don't you e-mail me-- oh...
You all right?
I'm just a klutz.
No.
What? What?
It's not what you think.
I invite you to my
friend's house-- Gibby.
--I bring you an ice cream
cone, and you do that to me?
We were just-- you shut
your mouth, Benson.
I don't need your details.
You don't understand.
I saw what I saw.
You betrayed me.
You both betrayed me.
Gibby.
Listen, it didn't happen like that.
No, you listen, nerd.
Nerd?
I'm gonna beat you down.
Friday. Behind the gym. At 3:02.
And bring a mop for your blood.
02?
Hey.
Hey, Fredwich.
Hi. What's wrong?
Gibby texted me 10 times today.
What did he text you?
"I'm going "to make you bleed...
"...On Friday... ...At 3:02."
"I love you, mom."
"Wait, that last text "wasn't for you.
It was for my mom."
Well, that's what you get for
mackin' on his girlfriend.
We fell.
We know.
I know.
And I'm not gonna fight Gibby.
I don't wanna hurt the kid.
[Giggling]
I could beat up Gibby
if I wanted to, right?
That's a pretty shirt.
Well, Gibby is kind of thick.
Whatever.
I'm gonna go talk to him.
You can't.
He stayed home from school today.
How come?
Freddie Benson, mackin' on
my girlfriend, betrayin' me.
Unacceptable.
Feel me?
Gibby, I made you some lemonade.
No drinks.
[Music]
Spencer, we're back.
Hey, hey, hey.
Awesome.
Did you, uh, get the...
Yes, I got them.
Yeah. I love sizzle rocks.
Mmm.
Sam, listen, you can hear
'em crackle in my mouth.
Get your face off my ear.
You know, I'm getting a bad feeling
about you pretending to be dead
just so you can get more money
for your art.
A, the newspaper said
I was dead, not me.
B, look at these.
Whoa.
Dude.
Where did you get that?
Socko sold three more
of my sculptures today.
People are buying them for
five times more money
just 'cause I'm dead.
But you're not dead.
That isn't my fault.
Look, if people are dumb enough
to think art is worth more money
just 'cause the artist is
dead, that's their problem.
But still, isn't that
taking advantage of people?
I see nothing wrong with taking
advantage of the stupid.
That's why we have stupid people.
[Doorbell]
Ooh, that could be an art customer.
Hi.
Hello. I'm oliver Dixon.
I'm the art critic from
the Seattle tribune.
Oh.
You're the one who
wrote that mean review
about Spencer's sculptures.
Yes. May I please...
You know, you got a lot of nerve
coming here after writing
that stuff about Spencer.
He was so upset, he died.
Yeah, his last words were
"why, oliver Dixon, why?"
So what do you want?
Well, to express my condolences
and actually I would like to buy
one of Spencer's
sculptures if I could.
I thought you hated his art.
I do--I did.
But when Spencer passed, I
looked at his sculptures again
and realized I was wrong.
They're whimsical and inspired.
Well, it's too bad Spencer
had to die for you to get
that he's an awesome artist.
[Phone ringing]
Hey, I just got an idea.
Why don't you write another
article about Spencer
saying how fantastic his artwork is?
That would lessen my pain.
Oh, oh, then I'll do it.
I'll text my editor and let her know.
Thank you.
Good.
Let's get some real
money out of this guy.
Yeah, that's my girl.
So you wanna buy one of
Spencer's sculptures?
'Cause she'd be willing
to sell this one.
Oh, that's very dynamic.
Uh, 2,000?
4,000.
Oh, I can't afford four--
you killed my brother.
4,000 is fine.
I'll... [music]
Gibby.
Listen, this whole thing
has gotten way outta--
that was a chai latte.
Well, I'm gonna make you a die latte.
Yeah, I said it.
Nothing happened between me and tasha.
I was just talking to her and
she-- and you lost control
and tried to kiss her up.
I'm gonna break you.
Come on, gib.
Time to train, kid.
Good.
You're training him to fight me?
Why?
'Cause Carly asked me to go over
to his house and talk him out
of fighting you-- to no avail.
Oh, and the fight's not gonna
be behind the gym anymore.
There's been a change in venue.
To where?
iCarly.
You and Gibby are gonna swing
it out live on the Web.
Why?
'Cause who wouldn't wanna watch
Gibby pound the fudge out of you?
Let's go, gib.
Say bye-bye to your fudge.
Gibby.
Comin'.
My fudge.
[Music]
One spoon, two spoons.
Whoa, three spoons, four
spoons, five spoons.
This is not entertaining.
Hey.
Carly, come here.
Come interact with me.
What's the matter with you?
I can't take being dead anymore.
Being dead is so boring.
Quit being dead.
But I'm finally having the art
career I always dreamed of.
And it's worth hiding
in our apartment 24/7?
I thought so, but then I was
reduced to counting spoons.
[Doorbell]
That could be a customer.
Oh, Spencer.
Get the door, get the door,
get the door, get the door.
Carly?
Veronica?
Yeah.
I didn't know if you'd remember me.
How can I not remember
a girl my brother
was totally in love with?
You know, till you dumped him.
Yeah.
I, um, I heard about
Spencer's passing.
I just can't believe he's gone.
Oh, are the dead really ever gone?
You know, I used to think that
he was so crazy and too loud.
Too loud?
And that whole tux
thing was so bizarre.
Yeah.
But Spencer was just a
creative, fun spirit.
I wish I could just
hold him one more time.
You can hold me.
I'm not dead. See?
I was just pretending so my
sculptures would be worth more.
You're insane.
Why am I enjoying this?
No. No, no, no.
I'm a creative, fun spirit that
can learn to be less loud.
Wait, wait...
To be less loud.
No, wait.
Don't go, don't go, don't, don't.
I'm not Spencer.
I'm his twin brother, Spuncer.
Really.
We could do a blood test.
If you did have a twin brother,
why would his name need to sound
similar to yours?
[Music]
Are you really gonna do this?
Well, I can't back down.
Gibby.
He betrayed me.
Hi, tasha.
Hi.
What are you doin' here?
I miss you.
Nothing happened with me and Freddie.
Yeah, tell your story walkin'.
Can I stay and watch the show?
Yeah, sure.
I don't care.
Here we go.
In 5, 4, 3-- Freddie.
--2...
I'm Frank.
I'm a toaster.
And this is the Frank
and toaster show.
J-k.
This is iCarly.
And it's fight night.
For the record, I'm
totally against this.
I'm not.
Tonight, live on iCarly,
you're gonna see
an all-out bare knuckle boy
fight between Gibby...
...And our very own technical
producer, Freddie.
That's not the photo I approved.
And once the dumb fight is over...
...I'll call Freddie
an ambulance.
I was gonna say we'll be
checking in on the peanut butter
and jelly sandwich that's been
rotting here for over a week,
constantly recorded by
Freddie's surveillance camera.
Wait.
Uh, tasha, hold the camera.
Apparently, Freddie's lost his
mind, so we're just gonna try to--
I can't believe I didn't
think of this sooner.
Uh, tasha, over here.
See, the reason Gibby wants
to fight me is that he thinks
I tried to kiss his girlfriend.
I seen it with my own eyes.
Yeah, well, the rotting
sandwich Cam saw it too.
So now take a look at
what really happened.
See, Gibby?
Tasha tripped and we fell.
That's all.
Man, I feel like a turd.
Yay, no fight.
iCarly, where we make food rot...
...And rebuild relationships.
Yeah, um, we're gonna take
a little break here...
...So please enjoy this
emergency pre-taped video
of my brother Spencer filling a
sock with raw hamburger meat.
[Music]
I'm sorry I acted so turdy.
Bros?
Bros.
What about me?
You're back in.
Oh, thank you.
Hey, hey, hey...Later.
Okay.
Gibby gone.
How does he get her?
There's gotta be somethin'
wrong with that chick.
Oh, come on.
Gibby's sweet and cute and
fun and there's gotta be
something wrong with that girl
Repair and Synchronization by
Easy Subtitles Synchronizer 1.0.0.0